Lucy Kroll Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Client File, 1916-1998 (Box 1-736)
  - Glass, Joanna M.
    - American Modern See also Containers 212-213, Canadian Gothic
      - Miscellany, 1976-1980, 1986-1988, undated
    - Artichoke
      - The Actors' Company, Toronto, Ontario, Canada, 1975-1977, undated
      - Actors Theatre of Louisville, Louisville, Ky.
        - Miscellany, 1986-1987, undated
        - Photographs, 1981
      - Alberta Theatre Projects, Calgary, Alberta, Canada, 1977-1979
      - Alley Theatre, Houston, Tex.
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1976-1979, undated
        - Miscellany, 1978-1979, undated
        - Photographs, undated
      - American Heartland Theatre Company, Kansas City, Mo., 1987-1988, undated
      - American Stage Festival, Milford, N.H., 1979, undated
      - Arbor Theatre Company, Peterborough, Ontario, Canada, 1983, undated
      - The Arts Club Theatre, Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada, 1977-1978
      - Barksdale Theatre at Hanover Tavern, Hanover, Va., 1987-1988, undated (Box 207)
      - The Barn Dinner Theatre, Cedar Crest, N.Mex., 1982-1983, undated
      - Barter Theatre, Abingdon, Va., 1984, undated
      - Bastian Theatre Company, Victoria, British Columbia, Canada
        - Miscellany, 1977-1979, undated
        - Photographs, 1979
      - Bathhouse Theatre, Seattle, Wash., 1979
      - The Belfry Cultural Centre, Victoria, British Columbia, Canada, 1977-1978
      - The Berkeley Stage Company, Berkeley, Calif., 1977-1978, undated
      - Camelot Little Theatre, Ottawa, Ontario, Canada, 1977-1979, undated
      - Centaur Theatre Company, Montreal, Quebec, Canada, 1976-1977, undated
      - A Contemporary Theatre, Seattle, Wash.
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1979-1980
        - Miscellany, 1980, undated
      - Cricket Theatre, Minneapolis, Minn., 1976, undated
      - Dorset Theatre Festival, Dorset, Vt., 1981-1982, undated
      - Film, radio, and television
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1976-1984
        - Miscellany, 1976-1982, undated
        - Notes, 1974-1983, undated, (2 folders)
        - Script, undated (Box 208)
      - GeVa Theatre, Rochester, N.Y., 1981-1982
      - Intiman Theatre Company, Seattle, Wash., 1978-1979
      - The Kawartha Festival Foundation, Lindsay, Ontario, Canada, 1982, undated
      - Laughing Horse Summer Theatre, Ellensburg, Wash., 1987-1988, undated
      - Long Wharf Theatre, New Haven, Conn.
        - Correspondence, 1970-1980
        - Miscellany, 1970-1975, undated
        - Photographs, undated
        - Printed matter, 1975-1981, undated
      - Manhattan Theatre Club, New York, N.Y.
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1978-1979, undated
        - Miscellany, 1978-1979, undated
        - Printed matter, 1979, undated
      - Manitoba Theatre Centre, Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada, 1979-1980, undated
      - Marin Theatre Company, Mill Valley, Calif., 1979, 1986-1988, undated
      - Miscellany (Box 209)
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1966, 1970-1987, undated, (4 folders)
        - Notes, 1971-1982, undated
        - Printed matter, 1981-1982
        - Production list, 1980-1982
      - Performing Arts Council of the Transvaal, Pretoria, South Africa
        - Financial records, 1988
        - Miscellany, 1988, undated
        - Photographs, undated
      - Persephone Theatre, Saskatoon, Saskatchewan, Canada, 1976-1977
      - Pheasant Run Dinner Theatre, St. Charles, Ill.
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1980-1981
        - Miscellany, 1980-1981, undated
        - Photographs, undated
      - The Playgoers of Lethbridge, Lethbridge, Alberta, Canada, 1978-1979 (Box 210)
      - The Portland Repertory, Portland, Oreg., 1987, undated
      - Press Theatre, St. Catharine's, Ontario, Canada, 1976-1981, undated
      - Red Barn Summer Theatre, Frankfort, Ind., 1989
      - Scripts, 1971, 1977-1979, (4 folders)
      - The Ship's Company Theatre, Parrsboro, Nova Scotia, 1993, undated
      - Stage West, West Springfield, Mass.
        - Miscellany, 1981-1982, undated
        - Photographs, undated
      - Sudbury Theatre Centre, Sudbury, Ontario, Canada
        - Miscellany, 1978-1979, undated
        - Photographs, undated
      - Tarragon Theatre, Toronto, Canada
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1976
        - Miscellany, 1976, undated
        - Photographs, undated
      - Theatre 40, Beverly Hills, Calif.
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1981-1983
        - Notes, 1982, undated
        - Photographs, undated
        - Printed matter, 1982, undated (Box 211)
      - La Théâtre Piggery Theatre, North Hatley, Quebec, Canada, 1987, undated
        - Miscellany, 1987, undated
        - Photographs, undated
      - Theatre Project Company, St. Louis, Mo., 1985-1986, undated
      - Totem Pole Playhouse, Fayetteville, Pa.
        - Miscellany, 1986, undated
        - Photographs, undated
      - Tricycle Theatre, London, England
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1982-1983
        - Notes, 1982, undated
        - Photographs, undated
        - Printed matter, 1982, undated See also Oversize
      - Victoria Playhouse Petrolia, Petrolia, Ontario, Canada, 1976-1978, undated
      - Virginia Stage Company, Norfolk, Va., 1983-1984
      - Walterdale Theatre Associates, Edmonton, Alberta, Canada, 1978-1979, undated
      - Westcoast Actors at the Waterfront Theatre, Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada, 1980
    - At the King Edward Hotel, 1975-1976, undated
    - Bad Counsel, 1989-1990
    - Canadian Gothic
      - Chappell Plays, London, England, 1977, 1987-1988, undated
      - Earplay, Madison, Wis., 1979-1981
      - Lunchbox Theatre, Calgary, Alberta, Canada, 1977
      - Miscellany
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1972-1986
        - Notes and printed matter, 1976-1986, undated (Box 212)
      - Rising Tide Theatre, St. John's, Newfoundland, Canada, 1982
      - Scripts, 1975, undated
    - Canadian Gothic and American Modern See also Container 206, American Modern
      - Arcadia Theatre, Buskirk, N.Y., 1976, 1989, undated
      - The Belfry Cultural Centre, Victoria, British Columbia, Canada
        - Miscellany, 1976-1977, undated
        - Photographs, undated
      - Berkeley Stage Company, Berkeley, Calif., 1974
      - Calgary Centennial Planetarium, Calgary, Alberta, Canada, 1973, undated
      - Centaur Theatre Company, Montreal, Quebec, Canada, 1975-1976, undated
      - City Stage, Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada
        - Miscellany, 1975-1977, undated
        - Photographs, undated
      - Magnus Theatre Company North-West, Thunder Bay, Ontario, Canada, 1976-1977, undated
      - The Manhattan Theatre Club, New York, N.Y., 1972-1977, undated
      - Manitoba Theatre Centre, Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada, 1976-1977, undated
      - Miscellany
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1972-1982, (2 folders)
        - Notes, 1972-1981, undated
      - Northern Light Theatre, Edmonton, Alberta, Canada, 1977
      - Persephone Theatre, Saskatoon, Saskatchewan, Canada, 1975-1976, undated
      - Phoenix Theatre, New York, N.Y.
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1976, undated
        - Miscellany, 1976, undated
      - Publication
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1975-1977
        - Miscellany, 1975-1977, undated
      - Theatre 3, Edmonton, Alberta, Canada, 1977-1978, undated (Box 213)
    - East, 1976-1977, undated
    - “The Guiding Light”
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1980-1982
      - Miscellany, 1980-1982, undated
      - Story projection exercise, 1982
    - Hagar's Children, 1978, undated
    - If We Are Women
      - A Contemporary Theatre, Seattle, Wash., 1993-1994
      - Greenwich Theatre, London, England, 1994-1995, undated
      - Miscellany
        - Correspondence, 1992-1995, undated
        - Notes and printed matter, 1993-1994, undated
      - Missouri Repertory Theatre, Kansas City, Mo., 1995
      - Script, 1993
      - Syracuse Stage, Syracuse, N.Y.
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1992-1993
        - Miscellany, 1993-1994, undated
        - Royalty statements, 1993
      - Vancouver Playhouse, Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada, 1994, undated
    - The Last Chalice See also Containers 216-217, Play Memory
      - Manitoba Theatre Centre, Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1976-1978, undated
        - Notes, 1976-1977, undated
        - Photographs, 1977 (Box 214)
        - Printed matter, 1977, undated
        - Royalty statements, 1977
      - Miscellany
        - Correspondence, 1976-1980
        - Notes, 1976-1977, undated
      - Scripts, 1977-1978, undated, (4 folders)
      - Transart Productions, Inc.
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1977-1979, undated, (4 folders)
        - Notes, 1976-1979, undated (Box 215)
    - Midnight Clear, 1978
    - Miscellany
      - Biographical material
        - Fact sheets, 1969-1989, undated
        - Miscellany, 1976-1982
        - Photographs, undated
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1971-1995, undated, (3 folders)
      - Document Associates, Inc., 1979-1980, undated
      - Dramatists Play Service, royalty statements
        - Books, 1977-1989
        - Performances, 1975-1987, undated
      - Notes, 1971-1989, undated (Box 216)
      - Termination agreement, 1989-1990, undated
    - Mrs. Boychuck, 1975-1977, undated
    - People of Raglan See Container 224, Yesteryear
    - Play Memory See also Containers 213-215, The Last Chalice
      - Canadian Association for Children of Alcoholics, 1987-1988
      - Ensemble Theatre, Sydney, Australia
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1984-1985
        - Notes, 1984-1985, undated
        - Photographs, 1985, undated
        - Printed matter, 1985, undated See also Oversize
      - Lunchbox Theatre, Calgary, Alberta, Canada, 1989-1990
      - Miscellany
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1981-1992, (2 folders)
        - House seats, 1984, undated
        - Notes, 1982-1986, undated
        - Photographs and prints, undated
        - Printed matter, 1983-1986, undated
        - Tony Award nomination, 1984
      - Production company (Box 217)
        - Contracts, 1977-1984, (2 folders)
        - Correspondence, 1981-1984, undated
        - Notes, 1981-1986, undated, (2 folders)
      - Samuel French, Inc., 1984-1990
      - Scripts, 1981-1984, (2 folders)
      - Theatre Plus, Toronto, Ontario, Canada, 1987, undated
      - Vernon Powerhouse Theatre, Vernon, British Columbia, Canada, 1988, undated
    - Reflections on a Mountain Summer
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1973-1987, undated
      - Foreign rights, 1976-1979, 1986-1989, undated
      - Notes, 1974-1987, undated
      - Printed matter, 1974-1975, undated
      - Proof, 1974 (Box 218)
      - Radio broadcast, 1975-1976, undated
      - Scripts, 1979-1980, (2 folders)
    - Remington Munroe, 1979-1981, undated
    - Santacqua, 1969-1971
    - Smile Maizie Clay, 1974
    - Surfacing
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1975, undated
      - Notes, 1975, undated
      - Script, 1975
    - Ties That Bind (based on Painting on Glass ), 1988-1989, undated (Box 219)
    - To Grandmother's House We Go
      - The Alley Theatre, Houston, Tex.
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1980-1981
        - Notes, 1979-1980, undated
        - Printed matter, 1980
      - Films and television
        - Correspondence, 1980-1982
        - Notes, 1980-1982, undated
      - Foreign rights, 1980-1981, undated
      - The Grandmother's House Company
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1980-1982, undated, (2 folders)
        - House seats, 1980-1981, undated
        - Notes
          - 1980-1981
          - 1982, undated (Box 220)
        - Printed matter
          - Biltmore Theatre, New York, N.Y., 1980-1981, undated
          - Miscellany, 1981
        - Royalty statements
          - Biltmore Theatre, New York, N.Y., 1981, undated, (2 folders)
          - Miscellany, 1981-1982
      - Miscellany
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1980-1983, 1990-1993, undated
        - Notes, 1981, 1992, undated
        - Printed matter, 1983, 1992
      - Scripts, 1980-1981, undated, (3 folders)
    - Towering Babble (Box 221)
      - Correspondence, 1982-1987, undated
      - Ensemble Studio Theatre, New York, N.Y., 1987, undated
      - Miscellany, 1982-1987, undated
      - Scripts, 1982-1987, (5 folders)
    - Woman Wanted
      - Book
        - Correspondence, 1982-1985, 1994, undated
        - Foreign rights, 1983-1987, undated
        - Notes, 1978-1985, undated
        - Printed matter, 1985-1986, undated
        - Serialization (Box 222)
          - Contracts and correspondence, 1984-1985, undated
          - Miscellany, 1984-1985, undated
        - Synopsis, 1983
        - Typescripts, 1984, (2 folders)
      - Film (Box 223)
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1975-1994, (4 folders)
        - Notes, 1975-1989, undated, (6 folders)
        - Printed matter, 1984-1988, undated
        - Scripts
          - 1985
          - 1986-1993, undated, (3 folders) (Box 224)
        - Treatments, 1979-1981
      - Printed matter, 1988-1989, undated
    - Yesteryear
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1971, 1987-1990, undated
      - Notes, 1980, 1986-1989, undated
      - Scripts, circa 1971, 1988, (2 folders)
  - Glass, Paul, 1960-1961, undated
  - Glasser, Barry, 1969-1970, undated (Box 225)
  - Goddard, Donald
    - All Fall Down
      - Contracts and correspondence
        - 1978-1991, (7 folders)
        - Undated (Box 226)
      - Notes, 1977-1985, undated, (5 folders)
      - Printed matter, 1978-1981, undated
      - Proof, 1980
      - Typescripts (Box 227)
        - 1980, (2 folders)
        - Undated, (2 folders) (Box 228)
    - The Benign Machine, 1974-1977, undated
    - Blimey! Another Book About England, 1973-1977, undated
    - Cheers (biography of Wendy Hanson), 1976, 1982, undated
    - Deadly Force (formerly titled, No Man's Land ), 1979-1980, undated, (2 folders)
    - Easy Money (formerly titled Black Caesar ) (Box 229)
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1976-1983, undated, (9 folders)
      - Miscellany, 1977, undated
      - Notes, 1976-1981, undated, (4 folders)
      - Printed matter, 1973-1980, undated (Box 230)
      - Proof, 1978
      - Royalty statements, 1978-1982
      - Typescript, 1978
    - An Enemy of Society, 1974-1981, undated
    - Joey
      - Advance reading copy, 1974
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1972-1978, 1987, undated, (5 folders) (Box 231)
      - Foreign rights
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1973-1975, undated
        - Miscellany, 1972-1976, undated
      - Miscellany, 1972-1978, undated
      - Notes
        - 1972-1973, (2 folders)
        - 1974-1978, 1988, undated, (2 folders) (Box 232)
      - Printed matter, 1972-1976, undated
      - Royalty statements, 1974-1978
      - Serialization rights, 1973-1974, undated
    - Kahn, Frances, proposed biography, 1973-1976, undated
    - The Last Days of Dietrich Bonhoeffer
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1974-1991, undated, (3 folders)
      - Miscellany, 1974-1978, 1984, 1991, undated
      - Page proofs, 1976
    - Miscellany (Box 233)
      - Biographical material, 1978-1981
      - Correspondence, 1973-1982, undated
      - Notes, 1972-1980, undated
      - Printed matter, 1988, undated
  - Goff, Rex Victor, 1970, undated
  - Goldberg, Carl, 1975-1976
  - Goldin, Ricky Paull, 1992
  - Gomer, Steven, 1989-1991, undated
  - Gonik, Jacob, 1974, 1981, undated
  - Gonzales, Jack, 1959-1965, undated
  - Goodfellow, Joan, 1974, undated
  - Goodheart, Annette, 1983-1986, undated
  - Goodis, David, 1955, undated
  - Goodman, Dody
    - “The Merv Griffin Show,” 1966-1967
    - Miscellany
      - Correspondence, 1966-1968, undated
      - Printed matter, 1966, undated
    - Women, Women, Women!
      - Contracts, 1965-1966, undated
      - Correspondence, 1965-1974, undated
      - Notes, 1965-1974, undated (Box 234)
      - Royalty statements, 1966-1969
  - Goodspeed, Donald, 1981
  - Gordon, Roy, 1960, undated
  - Goreau, Laurraine R.
    - Just Mahalia, Baby
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1972-1977, undated
      - Notes, 1975-1977, undated
      - Printed matter, 1975-1977, undated
    - Miscellany, 1977, undated
  - Gorodnitzki, Diane, 1973-1974, undated
  - Gottfried, Martin
    - Kaplan of the F.B.I.
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1971-1972, undated
      - Notes, 1970-1972, undated
    - Love Time
      - Contracts, 1974-1975, undated
      - Correspondence, 1974-1975
      - Notes, 1974-1975, undated
    - Miscellany, 1970-1975, undated
    - Palm Beach
      - Correspondence, 1973-1977, undated
      - Notes, 1975-1976, undated
      - Scripts, undated (Box 235)
    - Thieves' Carnival
      - Contracts, 1972-1973, undated
      - Correspondence, 1972-1974, undated
      - Notes, 1972-1974, undated
  - Gottlieb, William P., 1954-1958, undated
  - Gould, Milton, 1968-1972
  - Gow, Ronald, 1974
  - Graham, Martha
    - Alvin Theatre, New York, N.Y., 1973
    - Atheneum Publishers, 1959-1964, undated
    - Awards, 1957-1965, 1973, undated
    - The Dance Through the Ages, 1977
    - An Evening with Martha Graham, 1963-1964, undated
    - Fiftieth anniversary of the Martha Graham Dance Company, 1974-1975
    - Martha Graham, 1961 See Oversize
    - Martha Graham: Portrait of an Artist (Box 236)
      - Contracts, 1966
      - Correspondence, 1959-1968, (2 folders)
      - Foreign rights, 1966-1967, undated
      - Notes and printed matter, 1966-1967, undated
      - Royalty statements, 1966-1971, undated
    - Martha Graham: Portrait of the Lady as an Artist
      - Contracts, 1964-1965
      - Correspondence, 1963-1967, undated, (2 folders)
      - Draft, undated
      - Notes, 1963-1966, undated
      - Permissions, 1979
      - Printed matter, 1966
      - Royalty statements, 1964-1975, 1983
      - Serialization, 1963-1966, undated
    - Martha Graham: A Selection of Photographs, 1960 See Oversize
    - Miscellany
      - Correspondence, 1956-1967, 1973-1975, 1982, 1991-1994, undated, (2 folders)
      - Notes, 1956-1974, 1991-1996, undated
      - Photographs, undated See also Oversize, (6 folders) (Box 237)
      - Printed matter
        - Articles
          - 1958-1962
          - 1963-1994, undated, (4 folders) (Box 238)
        - Invitations, 1961-1967, 1972-1978
        - Newsletters, 1984, undated
        - Programs, 1958-1975, 1984-1988, 1994, undated See also Oversize, (2 folders)
        - Publicity, 1959-1960, 1967-1975, 1982-1990, undated (Box 239)
    - The Notebooks of Martha Graham
      - British publication
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1971-1974, 1980, undated
        - Notes, 1973-1974, undated
        - Royalty statements, 1974-1976
      - Contracts, 1960-1973
      - Correspondence, 1964-1989, (2 folders)
      - Foreign rights, 1973-1976
      - Notes, 1964-1981, undated, (4 folders)
      - Page proofs, undated (Box 240)
      - Permissions, 1972-1973, undated
      - Printed matter, 1973-1974, undated
      - Royalty statements, 1971-1986, undated, (2 folders)
      - Transcript of audiotape, 1971-1972, undated, (2 folders)
    - “The Perry Como Show,” 1959
    - Random House, Inc., 1956-1959, undated
    - Television, 1957-1979, undated
    - Tours (Box 241)
      - London, 1962-1967, 1979, undated
      - Miscellany, 1956, 1962-1973, undated
  - Grant, Lee, 1955-1956, undated
  - Gray, Phyllis, 1984
  - Greaves, William, 1969-1970, 1991, undated
  - Green, Hannah, 1965, undated
  - Green, Paul
    - The Common Glory, 1969-1975, undated
    - Home to My Valley, 1969-1970, undated
    - Miscellany
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1932-1935, 1954-1959, 1965-1974, undated
      - Printed matter, 1973-1974, undated
    - Sing All a Green Willow
      - Miscellany, 1969, undated
      - Script, 1969
  - Greenberg, Emanuel Martin, 1976-1980, undated
  - Greenberg, Stanley R. (Box 242)
    - Miscellany, 1976-1981, 1988, undated
    - Script, undated
  - Greenberger, Howard, 1967, undated
  - Greenfeld, Joshua
    - The Boy Who Sold Dreams at the Y.M.C.A., 1960-1962
    - The Boy with the Plaster Cast Leg, 1959-1960, undated
    - A Child Called Noah, 1970-1987, undated
    - Clandestine on the Morning Line
      - Contracts, 1958-1961
      - Correspondence, 1957-1963, undated, (2 folders)
      - Notes, 1957-1962, undated
      - Printed matter, 1959-1961, undated
      - Royalty statements, 1959-1989
    - Geronimo!
      - Correspondence, 1983-1984, undated
      - Typescripts, undated (Box 243)
    - Let It Be Me, 1975, undated
    - The Mask of the Red Death, 1960, undated
    - Miscellany
      - Correspondence, 1957-1967, undated
      - Printed matter, 1957-1970, undated
  - Greenfield, Jerome, 1967-1968
  - Gregory, Charles W., 1970-1976, undated
  - Gress, David, 1959-1960, undated
  - Griffin, Jane
    - Correspondence, 1965-1968, undated
    - Notes, 1965-1967, undated
    - Printed matter, 1960-1966, undated
  - Griffith, Richard, 1968-1970, undated
  - Griller, Catherine, 1964-1965, undated (Box 244)
  - Grip, Alan F.
    - Correspondence, 1977, undated
    - Drafts, undated
    - Notes, 1977, undated
    - Typescripts, undated
  - Grossarth-Maticek, Ronald, 1989-1990, undated
  - Grossman, Suzanne
    - Alpha and Omega, 1982-1986, undated
    - Chemin de Fer (formerly titled The Chemmy Circle )
      - Arena Stage, Washington, D.C.
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1969-1970
        - Miscellany, 1969-1970, undated
      - Center Theatre Group, Los Angeles, Calif.
        - Box office receipts, 1969
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1969
        - Miscellany, 1969, undated See also Oversize
      - Miscellany (Box 245)
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1968-1977, undated
        - Notes, 1968-1971, undated
        - Photographs, undated
        - Printed matter, 1968-1969, undated
      - Phoenix Theatre, New York, N.Y.
        - Box office receipts, 1973-1974
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1971-1974, (2 folders)
        - Notes, 1971-1974, undated
        - Printed matter, 1969-1973, undated
      - Samuel French, Inc., 1970-1984, (2 folders)
    - Coup de Soleil, 1984 (Box 246)
    - A Flea in Her Ear
      - Center Theatre Group, Los Angeles, Calif.
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1982
        - Miscellany, 1982, undated
        - Royalty statements, 1982
      - Miscellany
        - Correspondence, 1983-1985
        - Notes, 1982
      - Monterey Peninsula College, Monterey, Calif., 1984
      - Redlands University, Redlands, Calif., 1982-1983, undated
      - San Diego State University, San Diego, Calif., 1986
      - San Jose Repertory Company, San Jose, Calif., 1982, undated
      - Script, 1982
      - Walnut Street Theatre, Philadelphia, Pa., 1983
    - The Grand Hunt (alternate title The Royal Hunt )
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1980-1981
      - Miscellany, 1979-1981, undated
      - Photographs, 1980
      - Printed matter, 1980
      - Script, 1980 (Box 247)
    - La Guerre, Yes Sir!
      - Canadian Broadcasting Corp., 1972-1974
      - Stratford Festival, Stratford, Ontario, Canada, 1971-1975, undated
    - His Mother, 1975, undated
    - The Lady of the Camellias (alternate title Camille )
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1977-1980, 1986-1987
      - Notes, 1977-1979, 1987, undated
      - Photographs, undated
      - Printed matter, 1979-1980, undated
      - Script, 1980
    - Miscellany
      - Biographical material, 1984, undated
      - Correspondence, 1969, 1976-1987
      - Notes, 1976-1980, 1986, undated
    - Nellie McClung, 1976-1978 (Box 248)
    - Number Our Days
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1981-1982, undated, (2 folders)
      - Notes, 1981-1984, undated
      - Photographs, circa 1982
      - Printed matter, 1982
      - Royalty statements, 1982